[Fragments of Truth]
[Episode 15]
The police have obtained new leads
on Han Shuang's disappearance
seven years ago.
I know.
What I want to know is
whether your approach is working.
He's starting to waver.
Give me a little more time.
He'll give up.
I can't wait.
The police have come to us already.
You're dealing with the police now.
Only my way leaves them no evidence.
Even if they get evidence on you,
you'll have to deal with it yourself.
After all,
I pay your brother's medical bills.
As long as the police don't suspect me,
I'll keep your brother alive.
Think carefully about what you must do.
Okay.
I understand.
You used the computer?
Oh.
I was just reading the news.
I'm always pushing you to sleep early
and get up early.
What's gotten into you today?
I suddenly realized you were right.
I guess a man really can grow up
overnight.
But you didn't have to do all this.
I rarely have friends over.
I can do a little tidying myself.
You need to get more rest.
I should help lighten your load.
After all, you don't earn money
just for yourself.
You also have me, this burden.
You brat.
Don't say that.
Don't worry.
I can support you.
My treatment cost over a million yuan.
Where did all that money come from?
It hasn't cost that much.
Once a donor match is found,
you won't need dialysis anymore.
Then you can find something to do
and give me less to worry about.
I'm looking for someone.
Hi.
Could I ask you about someone?
I have a question.
Is there a nurse named Xu Manman here?
One moment.
I'll ask around for you.
Hey.
Excuse me, sir.
Could I ask you about someone?
Sure.
Go ahead.
Xiaojing.
She hasn't come to work in a while.
This student named Shu Qi...
Does she work at this bar?
Her summer break wasn't even over
when she stopped working here.
Does Zheng Jiajia live in this building?
I haven't seen her in quite a while.
You mean Xu Manman?
She hasn't come to work in ages.
We don't know why either.
Why did dialysis take so long today?
Were you feeling unwell?
Oh,
I chatted with a classmate for a while.
You're even socializing now?
All right.
I'll cook for you.
I'm not hungry.
Did you eat out?
Uh...
Sis.
I need to tell you something.
I need to take this call.
We'll talk when I get back.
What is it?
Make up any excuse.
Get that cop to the corner bar
in Taishan.
Does it have to be tonight?
Yes.
We can't risk further delays.
I'll tell you the rest
when you get there.
What are you going to do to him?
Don't ask.
Think about your brother.
What were you going to ask me?
Sis, tell me.
What are these files for?
And what does Luoda Biotech do?
These are just patient records.
Patient records?
Then why are they all girls?
Huh?
Why did they never return to school
after meeting you,
never go home,
or ever appear again?
I couldn't just watch you die.
I had no choice.
What did you do to them?
I didn't do anything.
I only passed their information
to someone else.
Who?
I can't tell you.
Sis.
They were as desperate as I am.
You were their only lifeline.
They trusted you.
But look how you treated them!
I don't care about anyone else.
I only want you to be okay.
Nothing else matters to me.
Xiaowei.
Another one.
You're still drinking?
You've had too much.
You got here fast.
Didn't you promise to drink with me?
You're drunk.
I'll take you home.
Why aren't you asking why I called you?
Whatever you say now,
I won't believe it.
We'll talk when you're sober.
Let's go.
Sure.
But promise you'll come upstairs
for a while.
Okay.
Let's go.
Easy.
Hmph.
What?
Water.
I want some water.
Water?
Mm.
Okay.
Wait here.
I'll buy you some.
Mm.
♪I stand in a fire-tempered jungle♪
♪Withered leaves fall
as my strength runs dry♪
♪Dust swirls as I clench my fists♪
♪I strategize, my faith my armor♪
♪My defiance spills onto concrete♪
♪Even thick fog can't hide
my clear gaze♪
♪Let neon turn to thorns♪
♪Flying low as the stars shift and turn♪
♪Escape the maze,
transcend the challenge♪
♪The meter starts, breaking the silence♪
♪A beam cuts through
a crack in the wall♪
♪This rhythm and noise
echo through the streets♪
♪Don't be afraid. No one will answer♪
♪Why is that child crying?♪
♪The shrinking scar on my arm♪
♪Means I've grown up♪
♪You can trust me when I say that♪
♪The wound still aches♪
♪Like a biting winter♪
♪But a spark still glows♪
[Copyright in this complete short drama]
[Jointly owned by Beijing Hualu New
Media Information Technology Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology
(Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
Co., Ltd. ("YOUKU") holds the]
[exclusive worldwide rights to online
distribution and broadcasting.]